mrguider.org 2019-12-25

# Privacy Policy - MrGuider

Privacy Policy for [www.mrguider.org](https://www.mrguider.org/)

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at support@www.mrguider.org.

At [www.mrguider.org](https://www.mrguider.org/), the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by [www.mrguider.org](https://www.mrguider.org/) and how it is used.

 **Log Files**

Like many other Web sites, [www.mrguider.org](https://www.mrguider.org/) makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

 **Cookies and Web Beacons**

[www.mrguider.org](https://www.mrguider.org/) does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

 **DoubleClick DART Cookie**

.:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on [www.mrguider.org](https://www.mrguider.org/).  
.:: Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to [www.mrguider.org](https://www.mrguider.org/) and other sites on the Internet.  
.:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – [https://adssettings.google.com/authenticated?hl=en](https://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html)

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include ….  
Google Adsense  
Amazon

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on [www.mrguider.org](https://www.mrguider.org/) send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

###  **How Google uses data when you use our partners’ sites or apps**

Some of the services are served by Google on MrGuider.Org. Google uses its technology to serve ads to users based on their visit to our Site and other sites on the Internet. MrGuider.Org uses the following Google services:

  * Google AdSense.
  * Google Analytics.
  * Google DoubleClick.

Your web browser automatically sends certain information to Google. This includes the URL of the page you’re visiting and your IP address.

[Please visit Google’s privacy policy page](https://www.google.com/policies/technologies/partner-sites/) to learn more about how it uses information from sites or apps that use their services.

#### Mediavine

The Website uses Mediavine to manage all third-party advertising on the Website. Mediavine serves content and advertisements when you visit the Website, which may use cookies. Mediavine may collect IP addresses and location to serve personalized ads. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices to opt-in or opt-out of this data collection, please visit [http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp](https://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

#### Add This

MrGuider.Org uses Add This tool to provide sharing feature to users. Upon accessing MrGuider.Org, Add This puts a cookie to your browser to analyze sharing activity. You can opt-out of Add This cookie by clicking [here](https://www.addthis.com/privacy/opt-out).

####  **Email Correspondence**

We will respond to all those E-Mails send directly by the users via the contact form or other forms. User’s email address will never be shared with any third party. We will not send you promotional emails or other kinds of notifications.

###  **Embedded content from other websites**

Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites functions in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.

These websites may receive data about you, use cookies, embed further third-party tracking, and observe your interaction with that embedded content, including tracking your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.

###  **What rights you have over your data**

If you have dropped comments or signed up to newsletters, you can request to learn more about the personal data we retain about you, including data such as email address and name that you have provided to us. You can also ask us to erase the data.

This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for analytics, administrative, legal, or security purposes.

####  **How we protect your information**

MrGuider.Org strictly protects the security of your personal information and values your preferences for its deliberate use. We carefully protect your data from loss, misuse, unauthorized access or disclosure, alteration, or destruction.

  * We keep our software up to date and take a regular audit to improve security.  
(-)We use 2048 bit SSL certificate with modern TLS for the encryption.  
(-)We use the highly strong password and Two Factor Authentication everywhere.

#### Adjust Cookie Settings

You can change the cookie settings for specific browser and remove all cookies or individual site’s cookies or disable or enable cookies or manage cookies: –

### Changes to this privacy policy

Although most changes are anticipated to be minor, MrGuider.Org may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in MrGuider.Org’s sole responsibility.  We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to guard the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy rhythmically and become conscious of alterations.

####  **Your acceptance of these terms**

By using this Site, you imply your acceptance of this policy. If you do not consent to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of alterations to this policy will be considered your acceptance of those changes.

####  **Who can I ask if I have any further inquiries?**

If you have some questions about this Privacy Statement and our practices, or you have reason to believe MrGuider.Org may have failed to adhere to this Privacy Statement, you can reach us by email:

MrGuider.Org

support@www.mrguider.org

This website uses cookies to ensure you get the best experience on our website
